<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<seiscomp>
	<binding module="seedlink" name="raw" category="sources">
		<description>Seedlink plugin that transfers raw data via TCP/IP socket</description>
		<configuration>
			<parameter name="host" type="string" default="localhost">
				<description>
					The server streaming the data
				</description>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="port" type="int" default="65535">
				<description>
					The port used by the server to stream the data
				</description>
			</parameter>
 			<parameter name="miniSeedEncoding" type="string" default="STEIM2">
				 <description>
				 The data packets received by the raw plugin are converted to miniseeds and passed to seedlink. This parameter defines the encoding of the miniseed samples. The available options are: INT16, INT32, STEIM1, STEIM2, FLOAT32 and FLOAT64. The selected type should be compatible with the data actually transmitted e.g. transmitting integers and storing them as STEIM2.
				 </description>
 			</parameter>
			<parameter name="channelProfiles" type="string">
				<description>
					The list of channel profiles for the station. Each profile contains location and channel codes to use as well as their mapping to the raw server channel numbers.
				</description>
			</parameter>
			<group name="channelProfile">
				<struct type="channel profile">
					<parameter name="locationCode" type="string" default="">
						<description>
							The location code used by the data of this profile.
						</description>
					</parameter>  
					<parameter name="channelCodes" type="string">
						<description>
							List of channe codes used by this profile and the mapping to the RAW server data channels.
							The format is "chCode1:rawCh1,chCode2:rawCh2,...,chCodeX:rawChX".
							The RAW server data channels (rawCh1, rawCh2, rawChX) will be requested to the RAW server and named accordingly 
							to the provided channel codes (chCode1, chCode2, chCodeX).
							The raw channel is an integer number that will be requested to the RAW server as is and the meaning of this number is server dependent.
							The channel code is made of 3 characters: Band, Source and Subsource codes and should match the ones configured in the seiscomp inventory. 
							For a 3 component station a value might look like "HHN:1,HHE:2,HHZ:3" (channel 1, 2, 3 will be requested and mapped to HHN, HHE, HHZ).
							For a single component station the vallue might look like "HG1:9" (channel 9 will be requested and mapped to HG1).
						</description>
					</parameter>
				</struct>
			</group>
		</configuration>
	</binding>
</seiscomp>

